let data=[{
  "data": [{
      "question": "Which must be the first line of an html page?",
      "answers": "!DOCTYPE html,html lang='XX',head,title"
    },{
      "question": "What is a 'div'?",
      "answers": "A block of elements,Text,A list,A table"
    },{
      "question": "How do you call a stylesheet?",
      "answers": "link href='XX.css',a href='XX.css',script href='XX.css',stylesheet='XX.css'"
    },{
      "question": "Which have more weight?",
      "answers": "h2,h4,h6,h5"
    },{
      "question": "'title' is inside of which label?",
      "answers": "head,body,div,header"
    },{
      "question": "Which ISN'T a semantic label?",
      "answers": "div,nav,header,main"
    },{
      "question": "Which atribute set the language of the page?",
      "answers": "lang,href,method,for"
    },{
      "question": "How insert a table header in a table row?",
      "answers": "th,thead,td,tr"
    },    {
      "question": "How insert a row in a table?",
      "answers": "tr,th,td,thead"
    },{
      "question": "How insert a cell in a row of a table?",
      "answers": "td,tr,th,tbody"
    },{
      "question": "What line is under a 'thead'",
      "answers": "tr,th,td,tbody"
    },{
      "question": "Which atribute will expand a cell to 2 columns?",
      "answers": "rowspan='2',colspan='2',href='2',action='2'"
    },{
      "question": "Which atribute will expand a cell to 2 rows?",
      "answers": "colspan='2',rowspan='2',href='2',action='2'"
    },{
      "question": "How insert a text space in a form?",
      "answers": "input type='text',p,pre,h1"
    },{
      "question": "How insert a multiple choice of 1 answer in a form?",
      "answers": "input type='radio',input type='checkbox',pre,h1"
    },{
      "question": "A label 'body', have to be closed?",
      "answers": "Yes,No,I don't know,It depends"
    },{
      "question": "A label 'link', have to be closed?",
      "answers": "No,Yes,I don't know,It depends"
    },{
      "question": "How insert a multiple choice of multiple answer in a form?",
      "answers": "input type='checkbox',input type='radio',pre,h1"
    },{
      "question": "Which atribute send the data of a form?",
      "answers": "type='submit',type='send',type='enviar',type='dataSend'"
    }
  ]
}]